<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RPG Character Creation Quiz</string>
    <string name="main_page_text">Welcome to the RPG character creation quiz app!</string>


    <string name="race_question_one_page_text">I feel as if playing a non-human race breaks game immersion.</string>
    <string name="race_question_two_page_text">I prefer to be a jack of all trades as opposed to a master of one or two.</string>
    <string name="race_question_three_page_text">I value skilled diplomacy or the ability to haggle.</string>
    <string name="elf_race_question_one_page_text">I prefer for my character to be more far elegant and more intelligent than a human is.</string>
    <string name="elf_race_question_two_page_text">I prefer for my character to be part of a very rare and mystical race, such as elves or gnomes.</string>
    <string name="elf_race_question_three_page_text">I prefer for my character to be immortal, or incapable of dying from old age.</string>
    <string name="orc_race_question_one_page_text">I prefer for my character to be ugly and brutal. The humans in my characters universe might use stories of my kinsmen to scare their children.</string>
    <string name="orc_race_question_two_page_text">I prefer to be part of a large horde or monstrous creatures which utilize numbers
        to overcome their foes. </string>
    <string name="orc_race_question_three_page_text">I prefer to my character to be larger than a human, and much stronger.</string>


    <string name="playstyle_question_one_page_text">I prefer to fight my enemies from close quarters as opposed to from a distance.</string>
    <string name="playstyle_question_two_page_text">I prefer to figut using physical means as opposed to magic.</string>
    <string name="playstyle_question_three_melee_page_text">I prefer to fight on the frontlines, no trickery required.</string>
    <string name="melee_range_break">Would you prefer to take the range or melee quiz?</string>
    <string name="rogue_warrior_break">Would you prefer to play a thief or a warrior?</string>
    <string name="damage_heal_break">Would you prefer to deal damage or heal and protect your allies?</string>
    <string name="range_damage_heal_question">I prefer to heal and protect my allies as opposed to dealing damage to the enemy.</string>
    <string name="magic_physical_break">Would you prefer to attack and defend using physical or magical means?</string>
    <string name="trap_turrents_break">I would prefer to utilize my inventions such as traps and turrets to deal physical damage from a ranged position.</string>

    <string name="place_holder_page_text">It would appear that you prefer to play a character which is neither human, elf, orc, goblin, or gnome. More questions will come soon to determine what type of fantasy race you should play.</string>
    <string name="playstyle_place_holder_page_text">It would appear that you don\'t have a playstyle that you strongly prefer. More questions will come
        at a later date to give a more accurate answer.</string>
    <string name="human_page_text">You prefer to take on the world as a human or human-like character. Battle against monstrous barbarians,
        or undead sorcerers as a normal human. You need no special race bonuses. Numbers and a belief in your fellow man are all you require!
        Strive for greatness and hope your accomplishments are remembered; after all, humans are only one in a billion. </string>
    <string name="human_break_text">It appears that you like human characters. Would you like for your character to be human or human-like?</string>
    <string name="orc_page_text">You enjoy playing your adventure as an orc, or orc-like character. Beauty is for the elves,
        compassion is for the humans. You require none of these things. You are an orc, hardened by battle, and uglier than 
        piss. Strike fear into your enemies as one of an unstoppable horde. Gnash your teeth and let loose a gutteral roar orc. </string>
    <string name="orc_break_text">It appaears that you like to play Orcish characters. Would you like your character to be an orc?</string>
    <string name="elf_page_text">You are an elf, immortal and graceful. You possess wisdom long since lost by the mortal races,
        and use it to protect the last remnants of a once great kingdom. Prepare for battle, grab your bow or your staff, and protect your people elf!</string>
    <string name="elf_break_text">It appears that you like to play an elf or elf-like character. Would you like to play an elf?</string>
    <string name="gnome_page_text">You enjoy the mysticism of the elvss, but feel as if they are too large, and too proud.
        A goofier take on a mystical force for good is more your speed. Enjoy the game as some form of gnome or fairy. You can 
        become an adorable force, and one which should not be crossed.</string>
    <string name="gnome_break_text">It appears that you would like to play some type of gnome or fairy. Would you like to play a gnome or fairy?</string>
    <string name="goblin_page_text">You enjoy the brutal and savage nature of orcs, but do not need to be that large. Visciousness
        and your cruel sense of cunning will get you through the game. Strike off into the world as a small, but cruel goblin.</string>
    <string name="goblin_break_text">It appears that you would like to play some form of goblin. Would you like your character to be a goblin?</string>


    <string name="warrior_page_text">Well pick up your weapon of choice, dawn your armor if you feel like at, and start smacking things. A warrior
        is the most suitable playstyle for you. Magic is for the intellectuals, a bow for the agile, but you value strength and stamina above all.
        Step upon the battlefield with one thought in mind, victory or death!</string>
    <string name="rogue_page_text">Take to the shadows and ambush your enemy. You prefer to play a rogue and a thief. Honor and glorious battle
        mean nothing to you. You prefer to fight another day as opposed to dying to a superior foe. There is no shame in that, and you know it.
        After all, what does honor matter to a dead man?</string>
    <string name="mage_page_text">You are an intellectual. Your thirst for knowledge is matched only by your ability to retain information.
        During childhood you discovered that a keen mind can defeat a sharpened blade. Head out into the world in a futile attempt to quell the insatiable
        thirst for knowledge. You are a sorcerer, unbound by the limits of the physical world, rule or serve as you see fit, for the world is your book. </string>
    <string name="priest_page_text">The gods have always been your friends. You choose to empower yourself through prayer, enabling yourself
        to make use of their lofty powers. Light some candles, crack open a book of prayer, and channel the powers of the gods upon your enemies.</string>
    <string name="shaman_page_text">You prefer to utilize the magic of the elements to buff your weapons. This allows you to fight with
        powers beyong your normal melee fighter. Burn your foes with fire, knock them back with gusts of wind. Enjoy the options presented
        when you control the Elements!</string>
    <string name="paladin_page_text">You understand that your allies must be protected and healed to make an impact on your world. This 
        knowledge led you to become a Paladin. Utilize holy magic to heal and protect your allies. You are the protector, the bulwark that 
        guards your people, and you always place them first.</string>
    <string name="engineer_page_text">You enjoy making use of your mind to set and spring traps for you enemies. Bear traps, tripwires,
        turrets, it does not matter to you! You are an engineer and you will use your inventions to overcome any obstacle!</string>
    <string name="hunter_page_text">You like to stalk your prey and dispatch them from afar. Whether it be with a gun, a bow, or a spear
        your prey will never know what hit them. You are a hunter, the apex predator wherever you travel. For the hunt!</string>

    <string name="playtype_quiz_button">Take the character playstyle quiz!</string>
    <string name="race_quiz_button">Take the race quiz!</string>
    <string name="yes_button">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_button">No</string>
    <string name="strongly_agree_button">Strongly Agree</string>
    <string name="agree_button">Agree</string>
    <string name="neutral_button">Neutral</string>
    <string name="disagree_button">Disagree</string>
    <string name="strongly_disagree_button">Strongly Disagree</string>
    <string name="title_activity_playstyle_question_one">PlaystyleQuestionOneActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_elf_question_one">ElfQuestionOneActivity</string>
    <string name="range_button">Range</string>
    <string name="melee_button">Melee</string>
    <string name="rogue_button">Rogue</string>
    <string name="warrior_button">Warrior</string>
    <string name="damage_button">Damage</string>
    <string name="heal_button">Heal and Protect</string>
    <string name="physical_button">Physical</string>
    <string name="magic_button">Magic</string>

</resources>
